studentcom.co.uk 2016-11-27

# CableCom Networking :: Privacy Policy

For questions or comments concerning this policy, please contact us at:

Registered Offices:  
Cablecom Networking Limited  
3 Windmill Business Park  
Kenn  
Clevedon  
Avon  
BS21 6SR

Company Registration Number (Registered in England): 3188615

## Data Protection and Privacy Policy

### Data

In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, we Cablecom Networking Limited are a Data Controller. In order to process your subscription, we need to collect certain personal details from you. These details may include, where applicable, contact details such as telephone numbers and e-mail addresses, credit/debit card or other payment details. If any other personal details are required, we will of course tell you.

### Passing on your personal details

We may be required to pass on some or all of the personal details you provide us with to certain governmental agencies and third parties because we are required to do so by Applicable Laws. Except where expressly permitted by the Data Protection Act, we will only deal with the personal details you give us as set out above unless you agree otherwise. For example, if we wish to use any of your personal details for marketing purposes, we will tell you and allow you the opportunity to tell us that you do not want us to use those details for that purpose. We will not pass your details to third parties for the purpose of marketing. Subject to the exceptions set out in this Privacy Policy, we promise to keep all personal details you give us in connection with your subscription confidential. We have appropriate security measures in place to protect this information.

### Your right to ask us about information we hold on you

You are generally entitled to ask us what details of yours we hold and are being processed by us, for what purpose we hold and/or are processing them and to whom we have disclosed or may disclose them to. Accordingly you may send a letter to the Marketing Department, Cablecom Networking Limited, 3 Windmill Business Park, Kenn, North Somerset, BS21 6SR. We may charge a fee. We promise to respond to your request within 30 days of receiving the request in writing with the fee. There are circumstances where we shall be within our rights to refuse such a request.

### Your responsibility to provide/correct inaccurate information

If you believe that any of your personal information that is held and/or being processed by us is incorrect then please write to us immediately as we cannot be held responsible for any problems that may arise due to inaccurate information that you have provided us with.

### Opting out from receiving further marketing information from us

If you have previously registered with us to receive e-mail updates or have not opted out from receiving information from us by e-mail, telephone or post when purchasing products and services from us in the past and would like to receive no further communications of this kind then please write to us at the above address.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. The current policy is posted on our website. We therefore recommend that you read it each time you visit our website.

### Links to Third Party Websites  

This privacy statement only covers websites that we own and control. It does not cover links to other websites and accordingly any information collected by those parties that own and control those websites or their use of cookies. Please be aware that individual organisations operate their own policies regarding the use and sale of personal information and the use of cookies. If you have a concern regarding the way your personal information will be used on other sites then you are advised to read the relevant privacy statement or in the absence of such a statement on the site, contact the company concerned.

### Security

We take great care to ensure the security of this site. The data you provide to us is protected using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology. SSL is the industry standard method of encrypting personal information and credit card details so that they can be securely transferred over the Internet. This means that you can subscribe on-line with complete peace of mind.
